You know him?
He's Caileigh's dad.
I—Impossible.
You cannot trust anyone.
What's the plan, boss?
She has a daughter, huh?
Kill her.
You're not laying a
finger on my friend.
And that's final.
Were you the one
who did that to Young?
Age does really matter.
You're too young to surpass me.
You're trapped with me now.
Shout,
and I'll cut your throat.
Hi, miss.
Looks like you're
all alone here.
Seems like your
ride's taking a while.
Ezekiel Roswell.
Everyone!
Look for my wife!
Now!
Now! Move it!
Whoa!
That's so unfair!
I keep losing. I don't
wanna play anymore.
Sorry, rules are rules.
So, for your last question,
What was Roswell's
last order to his men?
Fuck shit!
Fuck!
I really don't know how
that blueprint disappeared.
Damn it!
Fuck!
Who's that?
What the fuck are
you doing here?
Venice, someone
might've followed you.
Don't worry.
No one followed me.
Okay?
So, what happened?
Fuck, the blueprint's gone.
Relax.
I can just ask
Aemie for another one.
Huh?
Are you stupid?
What if Roswell finds out?
Huh?
Alright, cuz.
Don't worry.
I'll have it.
Whatever it takes.
Dong! I have—
You're safe.
Whoa.
Missed me already?
I'm okay, Dong.
Whoa.
Oh my god.
Were we robbed?
Where the hell have you been?
Just went out to eat.
Eat?
You didn't even tell me
you were going out to eat?
I was with your friends.
Friends?
The last time I checked,
I don't have friends and
never will be having one.
Whoa.
He says he doesn't have friends.
Then what are you?
Why are you mad, Dong?
Because I was worried.
Is going off with
strangers your new hobby?
Hey, no!
They introduced themselves to me.
Let's talk.
Look at this guy.
He says he wants to talk.
But then he goes and leaves me.
Zeke.
Ugh.
The things you do for love.
I'm sorry for how I reacted.
Good thing you
realized you were wrong.
My fault?
Yeah.
Was that right?
You got mad just
because I went out to eat?
I was angry because you
left without informing me.
Okay.
Then I'm sorry too.
Hey, but you know, I was
actually calling you earlier.
You weren't answering.
I was trying to call you,
but I couldn't get a hold of you.
My battery was dead.
How could you call me
if my battery was dead?
Fine.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
Okay.
Apology accepted.
Who were you with anyway?
Hey!
Zeke!
Why?
Do you see something I don't?
Whoa?!
Zeke!
Your third eye is open.
Stupid girl.
I'm talking about the
dumbasses you had dinner with.
Oh!
Them.
Uh, Phoenix and Cyd.
Phoenix and Cyd, huh?
Oh no.
I'm so stupid.
Oh no, don't—
Don't tell them I told
you their names, okay?
They said it was
supposed to be a secret.
They have a surprise for you—
Surprise?
I'm so stupid.
What else did you
guys talk about?
Nothing much.
They just taught me
how to play pusoy dos.
And?
And also, oh!
We played truth or dare.
Then whoever lost had
to answer questions.
Questions like?
Like who killed Moo?
Where does Roswell usually go?
Have I met Yaji?
Just stuff like that.
They were really good.
They knew so much.
Are you okay?
Oh no, you're getting dizzy.
That's what you get
for skipping meals.
You're so stubborn.
Eat something first.
Here, I got some takeout.
Fries.
Ah!
Choo-choo!
Choo-choo train!
Now arriving at Santolan Station.
The train's about to crash.
Open your mouth, Dong.
There.
You like being fed, huh?
There, it's good, right?
This looks familiar.
Hey!
Zeke, why do you have this?
I gave this to Venice.
Venice?
Mmm.
Shan Venice Birkins.
Louie Birkins' twin.
They're my friends from Stonehurst.
Don't you know them?
She asked me for this.
She said she needed
it for something.
But she said she'd
give it back right away.
She promised.
Can you promise me
not to trust anybody?
Except me.
Okay.
Promise.
Why are you sad? Want more fries?
Here, have some more.
Mm, eat some more.
Good, right?
There, chew it.
Wife.
I need the final updates on the plans
for the launching of your toy company.
Can I get it?
Final plan?
Yes.
For the launching event.
Can I have a copy of your plans?
It's been what?
Two weeks since you
started working on it?
I think she hasn't
done anything yet.
Wife.
I'm asking you.
Like I said, she clearly
hasn't done anything.
I'll just finalize the guest list.
Since Aemie clearly
hasn't even started it.
Ms. Stonehurst, this is for you.
Ah, finally.
Thank you.
Ezekiel,
I brought you some lunch
from a very fancy restaurant.
It's pan-seared beef medallion
with a side of potato puree.
- I'm with Ms. Fiona.
- Me too, me too.
No thanks.
My wife brought our lunch.
Right, wife?
Ah, yes, hubby.
Yiee.
Hubby, hubby.
Allow me to present our
artisanal handheld beef creation
layered in a toasted brioche vessel
accompanied by golden
baton caught potatoes.
delicately crisp to perfection.
I'm with Aemie, sorry.
Nope. Still Fiona.
With collagen.
That's a lot of fancy talk.
It's just fast food.
That's so...
cheap.
I mean, don't you think that like,
I mean—
I have a gun here.
Do you want to meet
one of its bullets?
Ohh.
Whoa!
Can they go on a date?
A person and a bullet?
Wife, my lunch.
- Oh.
- I'm hungry.
Okay, okay, okay.
Say ah!
Good?
One more?
More, more!
Airplane, airplane.
Bro, do we still have a glass?
You guys?
There's a light over there.
Go to the conference room.
Now!
We have to discuss something.
Wife?
Okay, okay.
- More please.
- More? Okay.
So you want more.
Wow, good?
French fries are your favorite?
Lerwick.
do you know the name of
the guys you were following?
Those five assholes?
Not yet, boss.
But I'll find out as soon as possible.
Never mind.
How about you, Boulstridge?
How's Aemie's mom been acting?
Uhh.
I haven't noticed anything
unusual about Ma'am Alyana, boss.
Sure.
Lee.
Guardian Angel.
Also known as Fauzia Arcadia.
She's an assassin.
And also, she's in the
same mafia group as Kevin Alferez.
Wait.
Those five assholes I've been
following are part of that too.
But what I'm wondering is,
why is Lionhart with them?
Is he part of their group too?
Lionhart, we're not sure of.
But Arcadia and Alferez
are with the dumbasses, Cyd
Garnett, and Phoenix Strife.
Who are those guys, boss?
Those are the assholes
you've been following.
Moron.
Why don't we take those
guys down, Mr. Roswell?
Do you want to die, Lamperouge?
Don't fucking
meddle with my plans.
Relax, Mr. Roswell.
It's just a suggestion.
Wait.
So if those guys are
all in the same group,
does that mean Fiona's
with them too, boss?
You guess.
Yeah?
Want some?
Take a bite.
Ah, fries.
Want some?
I want nothing but your husband.
Wow, someone's really starving.
Now she even wants to eat people.
Why do you want Zeke?
Why?
Aemie.
You gonna do something about it?
Listen.
I...
love him.
And sooner or later,
he will be mine.
So keep that in mind...
Aemie.
Help me!
Help!
Wife!
Wife, wife!
Wife, enough!
What?
What do you mean, enough?
Why enough?
What the hell did you do?
You almost killed her.
Huh?
What did—
What did I do?
Get her out of here, now!
Ms. Stonehurst, let's go.
What did I do?
Crazy.
- Huh? What did—
- She's fucking crazy!
What did I do, Zeke?
What did I do?!
What did I do?
Huh? What did I do?!
Why did I do that?
I don't know, I—
I don't know, I was
just eating here earlier.
I don't know what I did.
What did I do?
Sorry, I really don't know.
You don't have to say sorry.
Sorry.
I don't know.
Hey.
Dong.
Dong, sorry.
I really don't know what I did.
It's okay, it's okay.
You don't have to say sorry.
I fully understand.
I know how it feels.
There have been many times in my life
when my anger
got the better of me.
I don't want you to become like me.
Am I a bad person now, Dong?
No, but...
What pushed you
to do that anyways?
Because...
she said she loves you.
Then she said,
you'll be hers sooner or later.
Then she did this to me.
She kept jabbing her finger at me.
I practically flew off.
Sorry.
You should have killed her.
Hey!
You're so mean!
Me?
You're the one who strangled her.
I'm just kidding.
Come on, Dong.
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
You're not bad, wife.
And if ever,
I will still love you.
I love you more than
anything else, wife.
Mr. Roswell.
It's okay.
Oh shit!
Porn again.
All of you, get inside.
What's so fucking funny, Lamperouge?
Nothing, boss.
Your blinds are flirting with me.
I know—
It knows I'm handsome.
Huh?
Let's get back to business.
We're supposed to do
our toy company launch
at the Roswell Corporation.
And now we're changing the venue.
The four of you will help organize
my wife's toy company launch.
And make sure to add Mr. Ferrer
as one of the VIP guests.
Oh, Caileigh's dad!
Finally, I'll get to meet him too.
For now...
I'll leave this to you guys.
Oh.
Dong, you're leaving?
Lamperouge,
I need your bike.
My baby?
Oh, Mr. Roswell.
I just bought it.
I'm sorry, but—
Oh, okay. Sure, no problem.
Here.
There.
Just don't point that gun
at my handsome face.
Cool!
When I get a gun,
I wanna do what he
does to Kaizer too.
Hey.
Why are you here?
Eze-
Fuck.
I can kill you whenever I want to.
No matter where you
are or who you're with.
Remember this.
The next time you lay
your hands on my wife,
it will surely be
the end of your life.
That was close.
Let's start, wife.
Aye, aye, captain!
Ow.
That's not fair, I just blinked.
That's cheating, I wasn't looking.
What?
Okay.
Hey!
Fuck you, Boulstridge!
Boul, you're down again, Boul!
Get it together!
Let's go, Ma'am Aemie!
M-m-m-monster kill!
You bet on the
wrong chicken, boy!
Good job, wife.
Nice one.
Where's my cut?
Nice one, bro.
Your mom.
Hello, mommy?
Hi, Baby Ae.
I'll sleep at your place tonight.
Is that okay?
Yes, of course you can.
Okay.
Bye-bye, mommy!
What did she say?
She said she's sleeping
over at our house tonight.
What?
Yeah.
Okay.
Training's done.
What?!
Why?
We have to prepare.
She's arriving.
Let's go.
- Hey, he said we gotta prepare.
- We'll get even next time.
There goes my
thousand bucks, bro.
It's okay, at least
I'm not Boul-dozed.
Boul-dozed?
Boul-dozed!
- Boul-dozed!
- You idiots!
Boul-dozed!
What's your mom's favorite food?
Uh.
Mom loves seafood.
Milkfish, snapper, mussels.
Tuna, ponyfish, grouper.
- Snapper, mussels—
- I get it.
How about juice?
Boss.
Didn't you say Ms.
Alyana likes juice, boss?
- How about apple?
- Shut the fuck up, Lamperouge.
Here, boss.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Get those junk out of the cart.
- No!
- We're not eating trash.
- Come on, just take it.
Fine.
Just one bag.
What? Just one?
Didn't you say the four of them
are having a sleepover at the house?
Then we need lots of snacks.
Just one bag.
Choose one.
Dong.
Do you want a baby?
Huh?
What?
Baby?
Isn't that one of the ten
ways to be a perfect wife?
Give him a baby.
So, Dong?
Want me to give you a baby?
Really?
You want me to give you a baby?
Hey!
What's wrong with
you? Are you deaf?
Hey!
Hey, Dong.
You want—
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
You didn't answer my question.
Do you want a baby?
Why?
What's wrong with what I said?
Whatever. I'm giving him a baby.
Baby.
Excuse me, coming through.
Ahh.
Baby.
I get it.
- Right, a baby.
- Baby.
Come on.
Push it.
Push this.
- Come on, push it.
- Fine, I'll do it.
Oh, ma'am. I'll do it, I'll do it.
You push.
Hey, grab another one.
Get one more, hurry!
That one, that one, that one.
Geez!
Oh.
What took you so long?
This isn't close to the supermarket.
So.
What's new with Aemie?
I don't know.
Useless.
I thought you said your
real job is to spy on her.
It is.
Whatever, I'll handle it.
I'm gonna continue my
goody-goody friend act with her.
She's so gullible anyway.
Did you hear what happened
to Phoenix and the guys?
Yeah.
My mom told me.
I told her that it's better to
kill off both Yaji and Roswell
as soon as possible.
I'd love that.
Can I be the one to kill Aemie girl?
You know,
You know, I'm really surprised that
you're the one that wants to kill her.
Girl, I told you before, right?
I found out from my mom that
Auntie Alyana is the one that's
responsible for my father's death.
So if I kill Aemie,
that makes us even.
At least her bitch of a
mom will know exactly what-
Who was that?
Who's that?
Mommy.
By the way, why
did you decide to
sleep here tonight?
I just came to visit you, Baby Ae.
Oh, let's sleep beside
each other later, okay?
No.
You'll sleep beside me, wife.
I'm her mother.
I came here to spend
some time with my daughter.
Apologies, madam.
But Aemie's my wife.
My house,
my rules.
I have the authority
to kick you out of here
if you don't follow
my house rules.
My daughter will sleep beside me.
You can't do anything about it.
I don't care if this is your house.
I'm your mother-in-law.
I will do what I want.
Ahh, uh.
Ma'am, let's go.
Don't touch me.
Aemie, let's go to sleep.
Oh, okay, Mommy.
Oh, Mommy, let's watch movies.
Then teach me how to act again, okay?
Wife.
I thought you were going
to give me something.
Huh?
Oh!
I almost forgot.
Good thing you reminded me.
Wait, I'll just go get it, okay?
Mommy, I'm just
gonna get something.
Wait.
Please.
So, how's the business, Roswell?
Oh, it's fine.
My wife is putting up
her own toy company.
I'm talking about...
the other business.
Figuring out how to navigate
deals in the face of many problems
and what the future holds is
enough to keep anyone busy.
Strategic plans keep
my business successful.
You need foresight to
be able to do what I do.
Except no one can do what I do but me.
How's your relationship
with your husband?
Oh, Mommy, we're married.
I'm the wife.
And he's the hubby.
But most of the time, he's Dodong.
Are you okay, Mommy?
I'm fine.
Mommy, is it okay if I go ahead?
I'm getting sleepy too.
I'm going back to Zeke's room.
Okay.
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Mommy.
You missed me, didn't you?
Yeah.
Awww, Mommy.
I missed you so much.
Bye-bye. Goodnight.
Goodnight.
You don't have to give me
a baby to be a perfect wife.
Because for me, you
are more than percect
to be my wife.
Hello, guys. Good morning.
But I have a hunch.
Roswell already knows everything.
We can't guarantee her safety
if she's under Roswell's roof.
Especially with how much he hates Yaji.
I'm scared to lose you.
You're probably just hungry.
You're starting to
say all sorts of things.
Come on.
Prepare yourselves.
We'll be having visitors tonight.
Well, guys?
Condolences in advance.
Asshole.
Dong.
Dong, where are you?
Dodong!
Dong.
Where are you, Dong?